Q Lahore, Pakistan

Ch M. Kashif Javed

Problem Solver. Quick Learner. Firefighter.

I'm a self-motivated, tech enthusiast with good communication skills, I look forward to learn new technologies and set a mark in the market. I currently have a good understanding of Full Stack Web development with Reactjs, Nextjs, Bootstrap & Tailwind CSS, SASS, Angular, Asp.NET Core 3.x, WebAPI and have worked with Google Maps api, Third party Login Integration with Firebase, Machine Learning, CMS e.g. Wordpress, Shopify, WooCommerce, etc.

Resume Online: https://chkashifjaved.github.io

Professional Experience / 3 Years

ASSOSIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER (NEXTJS, .NET CORE) / MARCHE TECH STUDIO INC - Lahore, Pakistan

May 2021 - Present

themarche.ca, bazaarr.pk (Nextjs projects on which I developed components, and worked)

- Frontend: Nextjs
- Backend: Asp.NET Core

These both products have private UMS and ComplianceWeb Consoles. ComplianceWeb project is developed by me, and UMS by my seniors.

ComplianceWeb:

- Frontend: Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, Datatables.
- Backend: Asp.NET Core, EF Core (lambda queries), and consumed their other private APIs.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER & ML PROGRAMMER / MEDRUUM HEALTH SERVICES (PRIVATE) LIMITED - Lahore, Pakistan

Apr 2020 - Jan 2021

Bahmni (MRS), a medical record open-source system.

- Frontend: Bootstrap, Angular, SASS
- Backend: Custom Framework (Core PHP)
- ML: Python, Tensorflow, Transfer Learning (I was working n researching on health e.g. lung cancer, heart issues, chest cancer, maleria .etc. issues to be detected by machine using Al and machine learning n deep learning).

Patient-Nurse Matching System:

- Frontend: Bootstrap
- Backend: Custom Framework (Core PHP)

JUNIOR DEVELOPER (LARAVEL) / BLUEHORN TECHNOLOGIES - Lahore, Pakistan

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

Food Delivery App: US client project, developed from scratch with Merchant Panel and stripe payment gateway integration.

- Frontend: Bootstrap
- Backend: Laravel

Education

UET SCOCS / Bachelors , Information Technology (2020) / 3.4 CGPA

(Lahore)

Garrison Boys Intermediate College and High School / Intermediate/A-Level , Computer Science (2016) / 86%

(Lahore)

St. Stephen High School / Matriculation/O-Level , Computer Science (2014) / 80%

(Lahore)

Certifications

Natural Language Processing in Tensorflow

Starting Apr 2020

Coursera & Deeplearning.ai

coursera.org/verify/N3MXWQ7B5BAD

Machine Learning - Fundamentals

Starting Apr 2020

Youaccel

Intro to Tensorflow for AI, ML and DL

Starting Apr 2020

Coursera & Deeplearning.ai

coursera.org/verify/3R7SC28XL6HU

Web Scraping and API Fundamentals in Python

Starting Apr 2020

365 Datascience

Arduino using Blocky (Google Blocks)

Starting Sep 2019

			Starting Aug 2019
<u>a</u>			Starting Mar 2019
Angular C# Github Deskt Laravel PHP SASS Tensorflow	op (Git)	Asp.NET Core CSS 3 HTML 5 Nextjs Python SQL TypeScript	
Smart Display Monitoring System / Final Year Project Tools: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Python, Tensorflow, Keras Monitor displayed products smartly using ML and DL. Console App - Payroll Management System / OOP & File Handling, Semeter Project Tools: C++, OOP, File Handling			
Chrome Extention (Bulk Image Downloader) / Harward CS50 Project Tools: Javascript, Chrome APIs Awards IT Quiz Competition Runner UET iTec19, 2019			
	Hobbies		
	Angular C# Github Deskt Laravel PHP SASS Tensorflow ter Project i al Year Project Tensorflow, Keras d DL. tem / OOP & File Ha	Angular Github Desktop (Git) Laravel PHP SASS Tensorflow ter Project Tensorflow, Keras DL. tem / OOP & File Handling, Semeter Project ader) / Harward CS50 Project Industries Industries Information Technology	Asp.NET Core C# CSS 3 HTML 5 Nextjs Nextjs Nextjs SQL TypeScript Tensorflow TypeScript Industries Information Technology Hobbies

English - Medium